https://www.lifepositive.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us.
We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how our company collects information from all end users of our Internet services including those who access some of our Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors"). This Policy also explains what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors have concerning the collection and use of such information. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.
Personal information our company collects and how it is used.
Introduction
Visitors may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process (or at any other time) is used primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Products and Services. Your information will never be licensed or sold to any third party. However, we may make limited disclosure of personal information under the specific circumstances described below.
Responses to email inquiries
When Visitors send email inquiries to our company, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. Our company does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.
Automatic collection of information
Cookies: Our Company may use "Cookies" to collect information. Cookies are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive, at a web site's request. Our Company Cookies do not contain any personal information, but are used primarily as follows:
•	to keep track of temporary information. For example, Cookies allow us to keep track of the pictures you upload and download;
•	to register you in special programs. Cookies allow us to remember you when you login to the places on our site that require Membership;
•	to remember your country and language preferences;
•	to help us understand the size of our audience and traffic patterns;
•	to collect and record information about what you viewed on our Web site and what you viewed in our e-mail;
•	to manage and present site information and the pictures displayed on your computer, and
•	to deliver information specific to your interests.
Disabling Cookies : If you are uncomfortable with the collection of such information through the use of Cookies and Beacons, we recommend disabling these features through your browser preferences, though please understand this will limit the performance and functionality of our Company's Web site. Your browser documentation should provide specific procedures for disabling cookie and beacon support.
You may also opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page:
http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/
Or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics Opt-out page.
http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
Public forums
Some parts of our site may enable you to participate in public services such as discussion boards, chats, and live events. Please use discretion when posting personal information about yourself when using these services. Be aware that when you disclose personal information at these sites, such as your name, member name, email address, etc., the information may be collected and used by others to send unsolicited email. The services are open to the public, and what you post there can be seen by anyone and is not protected. We try to moderate the comments as best we can but we can't guarantee total control of the comments that you may receive while you participate in these services. Sometimes, you may find other people's comments to be offensive, harmful or inaccurate.
Our company's commitment to data security
We implement a variety of administrative, managerial, and technical security measures to help protect your personal information. Our Company has various internal control standards which relate specifically to the handling of personal information. These include certain controls to help safeguard the information we collect online. Our employees are trained to understand and comply with these controls and we communicate our Privacy Notice, practices and guidelines to our employees. However, while we strive to protect your personal information, you must also take steps to protect your information. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal information while you are on the Internet.
Services and Web sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.
Confidentiality of Information
Life Positive provides its services in SaaS (Software as a Service) model, and will host data and information. It will not review, share, distribute, or reference any User or Expert data except as provided in the terms of use, or as may be required by law. Individual records of User data may be viewed or accessed only for the purpose of resolving a problem, support issues, or suspected violation of the terms of use, or as may be required by law. We would take all possible precautions for maintaining the confidentiality of data.
Revisions to this policy
Our Company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms Of Use, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this posting.
Please feel free to reach out to us at info@lifepositive.net in case you have any specific queries
×
User
Partner Expert
Login
Register
or login without password through otp.
Forgot Password?
Your details will be kept strictly confidential
+91
+1-684
+376
+244
+1-264
+672
+1-268
+520
Forget Password ?
By Registering / Logging in, You accept our terms of use & privacy policy
×
Life Positive follows a stringent review publishing mechanism. Every review received undergoes -
1. A mobile number and email ID verification check
2. Analysis by our seeker happiness team to double check for authenticity
3. Cross-checking, if required, by speaking to the seeker posting the review
Only after we're satisfied about the authenticity of a review is it allowed to go live on our website
×
Our award winning customer care team is available from 9 a.m to 9 p.m everyday
×
The Life Positive seal of trust implies:-
Standards guarantee:
All our healers and therapists undergo training and/or certification from authorized bodies before becoming professionals. They have a minimum professional experience of one year
Genuineness guarantee:
All our healers and therapists are genuinely passionate about doing service. They do their very best to help seekers (patients) live better lives.
Payment security:
All payments made to our healers are secure up to the point wherein if any session is paid for, it will be honoured dutifully and delivered promptly
Anonymity guarantee:
Every seekers (patients) details will always remain 100% confidential and will never be disclosed
×
Please call us on +919650083789 to place an order
